《纸牌屋》前情提要...
Previously on House of Cards...
我很荣幸能够...
It is my great honor
代表总统 授予艾莉西娅·汉普顿将军
to formerly recognize the selection of General Dalton McGinnis
美军欧洲司令部司令一职
as Commander of the United States Strategic Command.
总统与我希望两位再接再厉
The President and I are grateful for their continued service.
是他  大一那年
It was him. Freshman year.
我使劲推 用尽全力推他的脸
I pressed my hand... With everything I could.
我使足了劲  弄伤了他的鼻子
I pressed it so hard. I broke his nose.
但那没能阻止他
That didn't stop him.
您好
Hello?
知道是谁发的帖子吗
Any idea who's making the posts?
深网论坛 很可能就是一个人
Deep Web forums. Lone wolf, most likely.
他肯定在和佐伊一起调查
He must have been working with Zoe.
-对着麦克风说话    -你是谁
- Speak into the microphone.   - Who are you?
你为什么要联系我
Why did you contact me?
因为你走投无路了
Because you're desperate.
你去找到这个人  把他关起来
I want you to find him and put him away.
他并没犯罪
He hasn't committed a crime.
但他有这个倾向
But he wants to.
几周后  等众议院通过这项法案
And when the House passes that bill in a few weeks,
我们就能结束政府的开销冻结
we will put the government freeze to rest.
你赢了  柯蒂斯 我们只想避免灾难
You get your win, Curtis. We just avoid disaster.
也许国家应该见识一下灾难
Maybe the country needs to see what disaster looks like.
我要的是个能管理好国会的副总统
You see, I wanted a Vice President who can manage Congress.
我的信念正在迅速地消失殆尽了
Whatever faith I have is quickly evaporating.
多数党党鞭办公室  杰奎琳·A·夏普
换了名字真不习惯
Strange not seeing your name up there.
"改变即是进步"
"To improve is to change."
"常变即是求精"
"To perfect is to change often."
很熟悉丘吉尔的名言嘛
You know your Churchill.
我离职去格兰顿-希尔时  你送我的表上刻的
It's inscribed on a watch you gave me when I left for Glendon Hill.
是吗  礼物的事都是南茜安排
Was it? Nancy arranges all the gifts.
她真了解你
She knows you well.
虽然我很喜欢跟你...
As much as I am enjoying this little --
我又争取到两票  帕崔奇和克劳斯
I got you two more votes. Partridge and Krauss.
雷蒙德是在向我递橄榄枝吗
Is this Raymond's way of extending an olive branch?
算个开端吧
It's a start.
两票太少  算不上树枝
Two votes is a twig. It's not a branch.
所以我来了
Which is why I'm here.
五点开始投票  还剩不到三小时
Well, the vote's at 5:00. We have less than three hours.
2小时49分钟
Two hours and forty-nine minutes.
足够我们拉票了
We have made more happen in less.
是我送的表吗
Is that the watch?
不是  比那个好
No. It's nicer.
雷蒙德为什么改主意了
So, why did Raymond have a change of heart?
政府停转对谁都没好处
If the government grinds to a halt, that benefits no one.
我们想让总统专注于中国问题
We want the President focused on China,
而不是为停转和抗议分心
not distracted by furloughs and protests.
听杰奎琳的安排吧
You take direction from Jacqueline.
她恐怕不会喜欢那样
She's not gonna like that very much.
不喜欢支使你吗
Bossing you around?
不喜欢见我
Having me around.
不怪她
Oh, I don't blame her.
阿什利会先问
Ashleigh will start the interview with questions
你和丈夫的相识  早期的婚姻
about how you and your husband met, your early marriage.
好
Fine.
然后会问一些关于你近况的
Then she'll move on to more specific questions
具体问题
about your recent transition.
好的
All right.
她还要问你不要孩子的事
She's gonna ask about you having no children.
不是说好不问这个吗
I thought we'd agreed to take that off the table.
是的  但他们一定要问
We did. But they insisted.
我可以直接找阿什利争取
Now I can speak to Ashleigh directly and fight for --
没事  以前也有人问过
No. It's fine. I've been asked the question before.
我知道怎么回答
I know how to answer it.
尽可能短  不戳痛处
It'll be quick and painless.
阿什利来了我跟她确认一下
And I'll confirm that with Ashleigh when she gets here.
这件不错
I like it.
还是别这么中性化
Maybe something less neutral.
你穿什么都好看
I'm sure you'll look good in whatever you choose.
我去楼下等
I'll be downstairs.
狄所里欠你的  你帮他搞定了天桥的资金
Disori owes you -- for the overpass funding you secured.
倾向同意  中立
-没错    -我给他打电话
- Yes, he does.   - I'll call him.
道格呢
Where's Doug?
四处巡视  巩固来之不易的胜利
He's doing the rounds, making sure our hard-won stay hard.
博奇和乌麦克也是  不过还是少15票
Birch and Womack are doing the same. But we're still 15 short.
我跟他们都有联系
Got relationships with most of these folks.
钱还不够
Money's not enough.
我试过民主党议会竞选委员会拨款的路数了
I already tried the D-trip route.
退休问题是关键对吧
Retirement is the main sticking point, correct?
老人也有投票权的
Old people vote.
我去找退休人员协会  应该能减轻压力
I'll target the AARP. That'll take most of the heat off.
这是浪费时间  我得去工作了
We're wasting our time. I gotta get to work.
带上雷米吧
Take Remy with you.
不该分头行动吗
Shouldn't we divide and conquer?
两个人更有说服力
It's harder to say "no" twice than once.
我尽量不碍事
I'll stay out of your way.
像《特拉华河流域法案》那次吗
Like you did on the Watershed Act?
这次我们在一边
We're on the same side of the fence this time.
你来晚了
You're late to the party.
就当雷米是你走投无路
Well, think of Remy as the guy who shows up
给你雪中送炭的人吧
with a six-pack after the liquor store is closed.
接下来见谁
Who's on your plate?
唐纳德·布莱斯
Donald Blythe.
见他不浪费时间吗
Do you really think that's the best use of your time?
除非他能说服别人
If I can get him to turn his people.
这么多鸡蛋放一个篮子里够冒险的
That's a lot of eggs to put in one basket.
可只有一个篮子
We only have one basket.
杰奎琳  能借用你的办公室吗  我比较恋旧
Uh, Jacqueline, may I use your office, for old time's sake?
全听副总统的
I serve at the pleasure of the Vice President.
2小时17分钟
Two hours and seventeen minutes.
有时间和耐心通常就能说服唐纳德·布莱斯
Normally, all I need to sway Donald Blythe is patience and time,
可现在我两样都没有
neither of which I have right now.
时间不多了
Tick, tock.
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
翻译 somehacker   痒痒   某豚   卫老哥
翻译 卢克·天意   章鱼X   喃喃
蓝光版调整  timhal@HDWinG字幕组   后期 饿得慌
顾问 老杜   校对 草草   总监 草草
本字幕由YYETS翻译 HDWinG字幕组修正 请勿去掉制作者信息
《纸牌屋》
第二季  第四集
唐纳德  你好
Donald. Good to see you.
副总统先生
Mr. Vice President.
别客气  叫弗兰克吧
Please, it's always "Frank" to you.
你找我  所以我来了  但我不会帮你
I came because you asked me, but don't mistake that for false hope.
抓紧时间去说服别人吧
If you have other people to lobby, you should.
十分钟
Ten minutes.
无济于事的
It won't change anything.
至少喝杯咖啡  反正不要钱
Well, at the very least, enjoy the free coffee.
我不喝咖啡因饮料
I don't drink caffeine.
那就脱咖啡因的
Then decaf.
那不还是咖啡因吗
Still has caffeine.
那就享受一下免费的氧气
Well, enjoy the free oxygen.
众议院办公楼那边待久了会闷
It's gets stuffy over there in the Longworth Building.
给我来杯咖啡  然后
Coffee for me, and, uh...
气泡矿泉水  如果你们有的话
Seltzer water, if you have it.
我们肯定有
I'm sure we do.
如果你记仇的话  我很理解
Now I can understand if you might hold a grudge.
我不记仇  弗兰克
I don't hold grudges, Frank.
我只是不和本性虚伪的人谈判
I just don't negotiate with people who are fundamentally deceptive.
我从来没对你说过谎  唐纳德
I never lied to you, Donald.
你保证说要和我讨论  结果你并没有
You promised to seek my counsel, which you never once did.
当时我们不得不把《教育法案》推到
We had to move the education bill in a direction
我知道你不会喜欢的方向上去
I knew would make you unhappy.
-我觉得不该去伤...    -你重创了工会的元气
- I saw no reason to frustrate      - You eviscerated the unions.
你把绩效标准交由联邦统一
You federalized performance standards.
我们要是不那么做  法案就完蛋了
If we hadn't done that, the bill would've been dead in the water.
然后现在你又想再继续克扣你通过的那点资金
And now you want to cut the pathetic level of funding you did manage to pass.
有点钱总比没有好吧
Isn't some funding better than none?
死了比变成植物人更能说明问题
A flat-line will send a louder message than life support.
听着  你凑出来的这个小同盟
Look, I, I'm impressed with the little coalition
确实了不起
that you've cobbled together,
-但是我们    -也没那么小
- But we      - Not so little.
28票  你需要每一票
Twenty-eight votes. And you need them all.
其实一半就够了
Well, really only half.
零的一半还是零
Half of zero is still zero.
为了让福利改革通过参议院
I had to pull every trick in the book
我什么手段都用了
to get entitlement through the Senate.
如果众议院没通过  我们没有再来的机会
If it fails in the House, we don't get a round two.
这是一锤子买卖
This is a one-time deal.
在参议院就不该通过
It never should've passed the Senate to begin with.
我们从头开始好吗  我可以向你道歉吗
Can we start over? May I offer you an apology?
我不想听  弗兰克  我退出了《教育法案》
Deaf ears, Frank. I withdrew myself from the education fight,
那是我必须抗下的负担
and that is my cross to bear.
但我一个错误绝不会犯两次
But I will be damned if I will make the same mistake twice.
你这么固执  沦落到茶党的档次上了
This sort of stubbornness makes you no better than the Tea Party.
只不过  我们是正确的一方
Except for the fact that we happen to be right.
再坐几分钟  唐纳德
Just a few more minutes, Donald.
你水还都没喝呢
You haven't even had your seltzer yet.
他们在东北部还有七个数据中心
They have seven other data centers spread across the Northeast.
那希望太渺茫了吧
Those aren't good odds.
如果我们能进入一个
Well, if we can access one,
我应该就能和另七个通信
I should be able to talk to the other seven.
它们都长那样  像是核掩体里的诺克斯堡
And they all look like that, Fort Knox wrapped in a nuclear bunker.
我们怎么进去呢
How do we get in?
不是我们  是你
Well, we don't. You do.
怎么进  我用什么理由进
How? Wh--what's my reason?
你要写一篇关于网络恐怖主义的文章  免费宣传
You're writing a story on cyber terrorism. It's free publicity.
但是如果他们安保那么严密
But if they're so secure, I'm --
他们经常安排参观  主要面向潜在客户
They give tours all the time, mostly to prospective clients.
那你自己为什么不去呢
Then why haven't you done it yourself?
因为我开了家网络安全公司
Because I run a white-hat firm.
如果我刚参观完  那里就遭入侵
And if I were to show up in the tour logs before a breach,
会引起注意的
it would raise alarms.
好吧  我进去之后呢
Okay, once I'm in?
服务器都是这个样子的
These are what the servers look like.
你得进入随便一个笼子里
You're gonna get inside one of these cages.
你拿着这个  插到服务器上
You will have this. You slide it into the server.
-就这样    -就这么简单吗
- Voila.      - It's that simple?
你要做的就这些  我可不是  代码极端复杂
Yeah. Well, your part. Not mine. The code's extremely complex.
我怎么做到这些还不被他们发现呢
How do I do it without them noticing?
和想要做好任何事一样
How you get good at anything:
熟能生巧
Practice makes perfect.
出了个状况
We've got a problem.
所有人  停下手头的工作  去最近的办公室
Everyone, stop what you're doing, head into the nearest office,
把门关上
and shut the door.
你  原地不动
You, stay exactly where you are.
退休年龄已经敲定了
Retirement age is a done deal,
但我也许能拨一些款项去...
but I might be able to redistribute some appropriations to oth--
那不是我想要的
That's not what I'm after.
你不能安个新轮毂罩就当修车了
You can't fix a wrecked car with new hubcaps.
一个姊妹法案怎么样  完全针对教育问题
How about a sister bill, one that focuses entirely on education.
我的同盟是在为党的尊严而战
My coalition is fighting for the integrity of the party.
-我们并不是只注重教育    -不好意思  唐纳德
- Tha- We're not just focused on Education.      - I'm sorry, Donald.
稍等一下
Excuse me for a moment.
南茜  我说了  勿扰
Nancy, I said, 'No interrup'—
什么时候
When?
但还有不到一小时就开始投票了  我
But the vote is in less than an hour. I
我才不管什么程序
I don't care what protocol it--!
隔离  邮件中有白色粉末
Quarantine. There's white powder in the mail.
我们被关在这儿了吗
We're locked in?
先生  马上把门关上
Sir! Close the door now!
听着  我必须
Look, I have to --
马上  先生  请关门
Now, sir! Please!
我得给我夫人打电话
I should call my wife.
我也得给克莱尔打个电话
And I should call Claire.
我应该告诉康纳吗
Should I tell Connor?
不要  媒体最好不要知道
No. It's better the press doesn't know.
检测结果应该能在投票开始之前出
The field tests should come in before the vote.
投票结束我就回家
And as soon as the tally's in, I'll come home.
情况怎么样
How's it looking?
挺危险  这次可能通不过
Shaky. We may lose this one.
那采访就难办了
That could make for a tough interview.
我本来就不想接受采访
Well, I didn't want to do it in the first place.
现在没法后悔了
Well, we're committed now.
我得回去应付"圣十字军"了
I better get back to the Holy Crusader.
检测一旦确认安全  就告诉我
Let me know as soon as the tests have cleared.
如果走运  是炭疽病毒
If we're lucky, it'll be anthrax,
我也不用亲眼看着法案不通过了
and I won't live long enough to see the bill fail.
别这么说
Don't say that.
会没事的
We're gonna be fine.
这样的隔离我们都经历过多少次了
How many of these quarantines we been through?
我都算不清了
I've lost count.
祝我能劝动唐纳德吧
Wish me luck with Donald.
土地爷保佑
Heels crossed.
-党团为此四分五裂    -当然
- It's ripping the caucus apart.   - Of course.
我们要一起坚持用我们这版法案
We take a united stand on our version of the bill.
我们有些人得立场坚定
Some of us have to stay on our feet.
事关党内团结
This is about party unity...
这是让我们放弃根基
It's about abandoning our base.
不  冻结开销才是动摇根基
No, that's what the Freeze is.
刀兵相向对我们的根基没什么好处
Our base doesn't benefit from sword-rattling.
只会搞得乌烟瘴气
It gets left bleeding on the field.
我的选区内的老年人数目在国内第三多
My district has the third largest number of seniors in the country.
如果提高退休年龄  退休人员协会得吵翻天的
If we raise the age of retirement, the AARP will raise hell.
我今早和退休人员协会的主席谈过
I spoke with the President of the AARP this morning.
他下周将收到一笔4500万的捐款
He'll be receiving a $45 million endowment next week.
选民还是会抗议的
Voters will still revolt.
中期选举结果不会好看
The midterms are gonna be ugly.
弗兰克·安德伍德  国会封锁  我困在这儿了
我们很多人  当然也包括我...
Many of us – And I can certainly speak for myself – are fac --
现在的选择是  政府立刻停摆
The choice is between immediate discontinuation of services
或是五年后提高退休年龄
and an age bump five years from now.
你是在拿假想的不适跟眼前的痛苦相比
You're comparing theoretical discomfort to imminent pain.
我只是觉得我们在跟核心价值观背道而驰
I just feel like we're losing touch with our core values.
《教育法案》就是个很好的例子
The Education Bill is a good example.
我们跟着弗兰克走
We all followed Frank's lead,
希望能靠他多少牵制一下共和党
hoping it would buy us traction with the Republicans.
失陪一下  马上回来
Would you excuse me, just one moment?
-媒体知道了吗    -还不知道
- Does the press know?   - Not yet.
能和他保持联系吗
Can you keep in touch with him?
我得想办法让午餐宾客从命
I need to pommel our lunch guests into submission.
你已经很接近了  放轻松  多听
You've got 'em close. But relax. Listen more.
他们想要的是支持  而不是打击
They want their hands held, not someone in their face.
我知道怎么拉票
I know how to whip votes.
请享用特区最好的鱼子酱  女士们先生们
Best caviar in D.C., Ladies and Gentlemen.
我们怎么能让你付钱
We can't let you pay for that.
那就别吃  如果吃了我也不会透露出去
Then don't eat it. But if you do, I won't tell anyone.
你刚刚说到《教育法案》是吗
You were saying about the Education Bill?
不  马乔里亲爱的
No, Marjory, honey.
记得吗  我们刚刚才说过
Remember, we just talked about it.
我刚刚在说...
I was telling you –
对  没什么好担心的
Right. Nothing to worry about.
如果有什么疑问  就去问莫里
If you have any questions, ask Molly.
她知道怎么回事
She knows what's going on.
我知道任何消息就会马上联系你
I will call as soon as I know anything.
我爱你
I love you.
马乔里怎么样
How's Marjory?
她还好
She's okay.
电话打得挺长
Long call.
你也知道  她情绪比较激动
You know, she gets emotional.
莫里休学了一个学期待在家里
Molly took a semester off to be at home.
我告诉她  春季必须回去
I told her she needs to head back in the spring.
我不希望她妈妈拖她后腿
I don't want her mother dragging her down.
你真是不容易
Must be hard on you.
我觉得女儿们更不容易
Harder on the girls, I think.
-她意识清醒吗    -一半时间是吧
- Is she lucid?   - About half the time.
勉强能明白自己恶化得多快
Just enough to be aware of how quickly she's going.
真糟糕
Awful.
我知道我不该这么说
I feel terrible saying it,
但我心底更希望她别清醒过来
but part of me is looking forward to her not being lucid.
至少那样她就不会知道发生了什么
At least then she won't realize what's happening.
我之前就该想到的
I should have thought of this before.
将心比心  而不是靠讲道理
Appeal to the heart, not the brain.
我对这方面不太了解  但
Forgive my ignorance, but
这方面的研究有什么进展吗
has there been any progress with research?
一些  基因测试  血管改造  但进展很慢
Some. Genetic testing, vascular manipulation, but it's slow.
马乔里赶不上这些研究的成果了
They won't come up with anything in time for Marjory.
所以我们只想提高生活质量
We're focusing on quality of life.
听着  我知道你还有事  我...
Look, I -- I know you have work to do, so...
我已经不是党鞭了  那是杰奎琳的工作
Oh, I'm no longer the Whip anymore. That's Jacqueline's job.
我同意见你  是因为我们有交情
I just agreed to meet with you because we have a history.
她很难拒绝吧
She would be tougher to say not to.
-但还是该拒绝的    -没错
- But still it would've been a "no".   - Yes.
我佩服你的信念  唐纳德
I admire your convictions, Donald.
如今像你这样的人凤毛麟角了
You're a rare breed nowadays.
你拿我们跟茶党比的时候  可不是这么说的
It didn't sound that way when you were comparing us to the Tea Party.
我不该那么说
I was being unfair.
你不是反动派  是进步分子
You're not a reactionary. You're a progressive.
我明白你的意思
I see where this is going.
什么意思
How do you mean?
我坐了这么久冷板凳
When you've been in the wasteland as long as I have,
对奉承已经有免疫力了
you become immune to flattery.
我知道你认为我是个本性虚伪的人
I know you think I'm fundamentally deceptive,
但我也能真诚地赞美别人
but I am capable of a genuine compliment.
那我就谢谢你了  但这不会动摇我的决心
Then I will take it as one, but it won't soften my resolve.
当然  否则你就配不上这赞美了
If it did, you wouldn't deserve the compliment in the first place.
如果你投了反对票  我也不会指责你们
If you vote ':no,' I won't hold it against you.
我们一条阵线的  中期选举也是
We're all in this together through the midterms.
但如果你们跟我走
But if you stick with me,
我们就让共和党和美国人民知道
we can show both the Republicans and the American people
我们不是就会闹僵
that we are capable of more than stagnation.
这是很重要的  就算会有些痛苦
And that's worth something, even it if hurts.
你们谁跟我走
Who can I count on?
收到
Copy that.
我们之间还隔着道门  我猜不是好兆头
The fact that there is still a door between us, I take as a bad sign.
一份样本检测呈阴性  一份不确定  先生
One tested negative, one inconclusive, sir.
所以我们必须把样本带回实验室
That means we have to take the samples to the lab.
那还要多久
So, how much longer?
还需要三四个小时吧
Another three or four hours.
我们有一项重要投票要举行
We have an important vote going to the floor.
我必须跟我的人谈谈
I have to be talking to my people.
投票已经延期了  先生
The vote is delayed, sir.
我们正在疏散国会大厦这一侧
We're evacuating this side of the Capital.
不投票了吗
So no vote?
在我们确认没问题之前不会投票了
Not until we get the all-clear.
好人有好报
Good things happen to good people.
还有一件事  先生
Another thing, sir.
所有的手机服务  无线网  座机
All cell phone service, Wi-Fi, land lines --
我们都会封锁  以防可能安全威胁
We'll be blocking them, in case there's a legitimate security threat.
我得跟我妻子保持联系
I need to be able to call my wife.
抱歉  先生  我们可以找人通知她
I apologize, sir. We can have someone notify her.
不  必须是我才行
No. It needs to be me.
如果是陌生的声音  会让她非常紧张
She gets very anxious if she doesn't recognize the voice.
议员先生  我被严令禁止...
Congressman, I have strict instructions not to allo—
想办法解决  除非你想让我把白宫扯进来
Figure it out. Unless you want me to get the White House involved.
我会想办法的  先生
I'll find a way, sir.
当副总统还是有好处的
There are advantages to being Vice President.
女士  我们得要求你暂时留在这里
Ma'am? We'll have to ask you to remain up here for a little while.
是因为隔离吗
Is it the quarantine?
国会大厦正在疏散
The Capitol is being evacuated.
应该不会有问题
We expect everything to be fine.
只是标准程序
It's just standard procedure.
你打不通的  通讯中断了
Uh, you won't be able to get through. Communication is being jammed.
我没法跟弗兰西斯通话吗
You mean I can't even speak to Francis?
确认安全之前不行
Not until the all-clear.
要多久
How long?
现在估计要四小时
Four hours is the estimate right now.
25分钟后就要录影了
We're supposed to tape it in 25 minutes.
我们无能为力
Nothing we can do.
你还好吗
You okay?
是的
Yes.
我去找艾玛谈谈
I'll go talk to Emma.
没事了  谢谢你
You know, I'm fine. Thank you.
艾玛
Em.
我们可能有点问题
So we might have a problem.
新闻里都报道了
It's all over the news.
可能还要一阵子
It could be a while.
我们能通过音频采访副总统吗
Can we get audio from the Vice President?
在疏散结束之前通讯都是中断的
Communications are being jammed until the evacuation is over.
你跟阿什利谈过了吗
Have you spoken to Ashleigh?
她觉得我们该弄辆转播车来  回头直播
She thinks we should get a sat truck down here. Wait and go live.
我没法保证什么时候能恢复
I can't guarantee when that will be.
副总统被隔离在国会大厦  我们有独家新闻
The Vice President is quarantined in the Capitol, and we have an exclusive.
不管我们何时开工  电视台都会转播的
The network will broadcast whenever the hell we tell them to.
他们会等你到达
They're holding off until you get here.
你应该独自做采访
You should do the interview solo.
我想等你
I'd rather wait.
谁知道我们能不能赢得投票
Who knows whether we'll win the vote?
如果我们输了
If we lose,
我可不想上全国电视台
I don't want my face on national television.
这或许也是好事
This could be a silver lining.
我不知道  弗兰西斯
I don't know, Francis.
你肯定会很棒的
I'm sure you'll be terrific.
我跟康纳商量一下吧
Let me run it past Connor.
好的  谢谢  我们说完了
Okay. Thank you. We're done.
先生  我们接通了布莱斯太太
Sir, we were able to get Mrs. Blythe.
唐纳德
Oh, Donald...
马乔里
Marjory?
-喂    -对  是我  亲爱的
- Hello?   - Yes, it's me, sweetheart.
听不清你说话
It's hard to hear you.
我们还被困在办公室里
We're still stuck inside the office.
什么办公室
What office?
在国会大厦  还得要一阵子
At the Capitol. It --it's going to be a l—a little while longer.
但你为什么去那里  今天是星期天啊
But why are you there? It's Sunday.
不  今天是星期五  亲爱的
No, it -- it's Friday, sweetheart.
-唐纳德    -我在呢
- Donald?   - I'm here.
跟我在一起的男人是谁
Uh, who is this man with me?
他是一位警察
Uh, he's a police officer.
他们用对讲机让我们通话
They're using walkie-talkies so we can speak.
我在跟谁说话
Who am I talking to?
是您丈夫  夫人
It's your husband, ma'am.
我没结婚
I'm not married.
是我  是唐纳德
It -- It's me. It's Donald.
关上  我不认识那个那人
Turn it off. I don't know that man.
马乔里
Marjory...
她去另一个房间了  先生
She went into the other room, sir.
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
能麻烦你陪着她吗
If you could stay with her, please...
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
喝一杯吗
Drink?
好啊
Sure. Why not?
他可能要到午夜才有空
For all we know it could be midnight before he's out.
然后他还要主持投票
And then he still needs to manage the vote.
凌晨两点我们也没问题
We're fine if it's two a.m.
大家都睡着的时候播吗
When everyone's asleep?
人们会为这个熬夜的
People would stay up for this.
关键就是想在黄金时段播
The whole point was prime time.
那我们明天再进行
Then we do it tomorrow.
我们已经为这个推掉半天的日程了
We've already set aside half a day for this.
副总统先生不会为一个访谈重新安排一整天的日程
The Vice President can't rearrange his entire schedule for an interview.
眼下也没有其他的选择
I don't see any other options.
我和弗兰西斯用对讲谈过了
I spoke to Francis over the radio.
我们认为应该我单独接受采访
We think I should do it alone.
只有你一人
Just you?
安德伍德夫人和阿什利  一对一
Mrs. Underwood and Ashleigh, one-on-one.
也许我们可以转播他的录音
Maybe we can broadcast his voice
弗兰西斯不希望访谈完全是关于隔离的
Francis doesn't want the entire interview to be about the quarantine.
我也一样  那只是个小插曲
Neither do I. That's just spectacle.
隔离是新闻  这是难得的机会
The quarantine is news. We have a unique opportunity --
那好  我们取消吧
Fine. We're done.
-什么    -取消访谈  不重新安排
- What?      - Cancel the interview. No reschedule.
别这样  康纳
Come on, Connor.
请你收拾好东西离开
Please pack up everything and leave.
好吧  我给阿什利打电话
Okay, wait. Let me call Ashleigh.
我以为我会逐渐习惯
I thought I'd get used to it,
但我没有  每次还是很痛苦
but no. Hurts every time.
你和一个人一起生活了三十年
You spend 30 years with someone,
而现在她甚至不知道你是谁
and then they don't have a damn clue who you are.
我真的不应该
Ugh... I really shouldn't...
如果我们不该做的事就不做
If we never did anything we shouldn't do,
那就体会不到做该做的事的成就感了
we'd never feel good about doing the things we should.
说的好
Excellent point.
如果这是我们生命最后的时刻
And if these are our last moments on earth
我不知道你怎么打算  我倒宁愿喝醉了
I don't know about you, but I'd rather go out with a buzz on.
敬马乔里
To Marjory.
你非常爱她
You love her dearly.
胜过其他一切
More than anything.
我不敢想象没有克莱尔我会怎么办
I can't imagine what I'd do without Claire,
或是如果她记不起我是谁
or if she didn't remember who I was.
但愿你不会遇到这样的情况
Hopefully, you'll never have to.
可你  或是任何人遇上这种事都让我觉得生气
Well, it makes me angry that you do, that anybody does.
没必要为你不能改变的事而生气
No sense being angry over what you can't change.
老年痴呆的研究有多少经费
How much funding does Alzheimer's research get?
不到五亿
Just under $500 million.
我不是专家  但这个数听上去有点少啊
Well, I'm no expert, but that sounds inadequate to me.
确实是  如果分配一百块用于研究
It is. For every $100 we allocate to research,
就得花将近三万用于看护
we spend nearly $30,000 on care.
得改变这种情况
We oughta change that.
我试过了  我的法案都没通过委员会
I tried. My bill didn't even leave committee.
谁反对
Who opposed it?
霍华德·韦伯
Howard Webb.
拨款委员会的
Ugh. Appropriations.
他都没让法案投票
He didn't even put it to a vote.
我向来不喜欢霍华德
I've never been fond of Howard.
我也一样
That makes two of us.
他的原因是什么
What was his argument?
他觉得他不欠我的
He didn't feel he owed me one.
"浪费开销"  他就说了这一句
'Fiscally irresponsible,' is all he said.
跟我好好说说你的法案
Walk me through the specifics of your bill.
我知道你要干什么了
I see what you're doing.
干什么
Doing what?
你真让人恶心  弗兰克
You're disgusting, Frank.
你说什么
Excuse me?
利用我妻子
Using my wife.
唐纳德  你在说什么
Donald, what are saying?
你以为你多给老年痴呆一点研究经费
You think I'll give in on Entitlement
我就会在福利改革修正案上妥协
if you slap some extra Alzheimer's funding on the table?
我完全没这个意思
I was not suggesting that at all.
胡说  弗兰克
Bullshit, Frank.
你可以随便看低我
You think as little of me as you want,
但我不拿健康作交易筹码
but I do not barter with people's health.
那你为什么要上调退休年限
Then why are you trying to raise the age of Retirement?
医疗研究  我们负担得起
Medical research we can afford.
医疗保险  我们负担不起  这是现实  唐纳德
Medicare, we can't. There are realities, Donald.
别和我谈什么现实  我妻子在渐渐死去
Don't talk down to me about reality. My wife is dying.
这才是现实  如果你的法案通过
That's a reality. Other people will die, too,
还有其他人会死  这才是现实
if your package succeeds. That's a reality.
该死的
God damn it.
真希望我没跟你一起困在这儿
I wish I wasn't stuck in this fucking room with you.
唐纳德
Donald?
我不想再说什么了
I'm done talking.
-再来一次    -我能行
- One more time.   - I've got it.
我希望听起来更自然
I want it to sound more natural.
弗兰西斯和我献身公共事业
Uh, Francis and I both wanted to devote our lives to public service.
而我们一致认为投身公职
And we didn't feel that we could both do that
就难以善尽父母之责
and be the parents we wanted to be.
所以我们作了取舍  让我们有更多时间
And by making that choice it allows more time for us
为其他人服务
to be in the service of others.
很好  听起来很好
Good. That sounds good.
请过来吧  安德伍德夫人
We need you, Mrs. Underwood.
让德里克待在国会大厦
Keep Derek at the Capitol.
采访被疏散者和国土安全部
I want quotes from evacuees and Homeland Security.
让萨拉完成生化威胁历史的部分
And Sarah should be finishing that history of biohazard scares.
我很快就过去
I'll be there soon.
我要走了
I have to go.
不行  我们还没干完
No. We're not done yet.
这是个大新闻  我明天再过来
This is a major story. I'll come back tomorrow.
那样你就是连续两天都是如此  这就有了规律
Gonna be two days in a row, and this is how patterns emerge.
联调局喜欢规律  我们不能去撞枪口
The FBI likes patterns, and we do not give the FBI what the FBI likes.
我不能一整天都消失  现在正是...
I can't disappear all day in the middle of –
我有八个记者正在外面跑新闻
I have eight reporters out in the field,okay?
别说了
Stop.
告诉我  我为什么要买腰果
Tell me why I purchased Cashew.
我不知道
I don't know.
为了陪伴我吗
Companionship?
是的
Yes.
更重要的是  提醒我自己
More importantly, a reminder that I am never
我距离被关进笼子里只有一步之遥
more than one wrong move away from life in a cage.
你留下来
You stay.
我让你看看我要写的全部代码
I'll walk you through every line of code I intend to write,
我每一次对防火墙的攻击
every attempt I make to breach the wall.
如果我们被抓  你不能说自己一无所知
If we get caught, you don't get to plead ignorance.
我们一起进去
We go down together.
不  我不是来玩雌雄大盗的
No, I didn't sign up for Bonnie and Clyde.
你需要我做这一件事
You need me for this one thing.
我也需要你  但无论我来之前你做了什么
Just like I need you. But whatever you've done before me, that --
你知道我住在哪里  你知道我是谁
You know where I live. And you know who I am.
坐下  我们越早开始  就能越早结束
Sit down. The sooner we start, the sooner we finish.
国会大厦依然封锁  防化部队成员
The Capitol is still on lockdown, as HAZMAT crews
还在继续检查整栋大厦
continue a thorough sweep of the building.
今天早上  一封寄给多数党党鞭
Earlier this morning, a white powder-like substance...
杰奎琳·夏普的包裹中
...was found in a package mailed to the office
发现了白色粉末状物质
of Majority Whip Jacqueline Sharp.
我们现在可以走了吗
Not are we free to go?
快了  不到一小时
Almost, sir. Less than hour.
我有一条你太太发来的消息
I've got a message from your wife.
什么消息
What is it?
她正在做现场采访
She's doing the interview live right now.
与议员唐纳德·布莱斯及夏普女士手下
...Quarantined with Congressman Donald Blythe
十四名员工隔离在一起  特情局...
and 14 of Miss Sharp's staff. The secrets
安德伍德夫人  我非常感激你
Mrs. Underwood, I so appreciate you taking the time to speak
能在今天这种情况下与我们对话
with us today in what, I am certain,
你现在一定很担心
is a very stressful situation.
谢谢  阿什利
Thank you, Ashleigh.
你今天跟你丈夫通过话吗
Have you spoken with your husband today?
是的  他状态很不错
Yes, I did. And he's in very good spirits,
特情局处理的很好
and in good hands with the Secret Service.
当然  对于不能来他感到很失望
Of course, he's very disappointed he couldn't be here.
我们的心与他同在
Well, our thoughts are with him and --
以及被隔离在国会大厦的所有人
and everyone quarantined at the Capitol.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我想要你在德克萨斯州
I'd like to begin with Claire Underwood
遇到你丈夫之前开始说起
before she met her husband, in Texas.
我有一些照片
And I have a couple of pictures.
-不会吧    -是的
- Oh, no.   - Yes.
天呐  那是红鬃
Oh. My goodness. That was Red.
你是个熟练的骑手吗
An accomplished rider?
狂热的骑手
Uh, an enthusiast.
这张是几年以后的照片
This one's from a couple of years later.
天呐
Oh, my goodness.
你喜欢这双皮便鞋吗
You like those penny loafers?
妙极了
Those are wonder—
这是两个截然不同的女孩
Those are two very different girls.
你更喜欢做哪一个
Which one are you more comfortable being?
我家的农场  那是我的家园
My family's ranch. That was home…for me.
你不喜欢预科学校吗
You didn't like the prep school?
不  我想我更喜欢泥巴
No. I think I preferred the dirt.
但你在达拉斯长大  在高地公园
You grew up in – in Dallas, though. Um, Highland Park.
是的  我父亲  他是个生意人
Yes. My father, um, well, he was a businessman,
所以我们住在城里  但我们是农场主
So we lived in the city, but we're ranchers.
我们家过去三代人都是
I mean, we – we go back three generations, our family.
你父母非常有钱
Your parents were very wealthy.
我们过得很舒坦  没错
Uh, we were comfortable, yes.
他们让我应有尽有
They made sure I wanted for nothing.
的确是个快乐的童年
It was a very happy childhood.
那段时间你最鲜活的记忆是什么
What is your most vivid memory from that time?
我"最鲜活的记忆"
My 'most vivid memory.'
可能是我九岁或十岁的时候
Probably when I was about nine or ten,
我父亲带我去了肯尼迪遇刺的迪利广场
my father took me to Dealey Plaza, where Kennedy was shot.
他说"克莱尔  一位伟人死在这里"
And he said, 'Claire, a great man died here.'
我记得我当时还不完全理解死亡的概念
And I remember not fully comprehending the meaning of death yet.
我问他总统怎么死的  他就跟我说了
And I asked him how he died, and he told me.
我记得我感到十分难过和愤怒
And I remember feeling so sad, so angry.
这太不公平了
It seemed so unfair.
我哭了起来  然我后父亲抱起我
I started to cry, and my daddy picked me up.
他用胳膊搂着我
And he wrapped his arms around me,
然后说道  "别伤心  宝贝儿
and he said, 'Don't be sad, sweetheart.
他让世界变得更好了
"He made the world a better place,
但有时这是要付出代价的"
but sometimes that comes at a price.'
我想这就是我最鲜活的记忆了
I guess that was the most vivid memory.
我们就差八票了
We are only eight votes away.
抱歉  我心意已决
I'm sorry. I've made up my mind.
我也一样  我得坚持立场
Me, too. I've gotta stick to my guns on this one.
你们宁愿让政府关门...
You would rather let the government shut down --
你注意点
Hey, hey, hey.
这你怨不着我们
Don't put that on us
谁叫党鞭大人最后才想起来我们
just because we're on the ass-end of the whip list.
别误会  我们都很敬重你  杰姬
Don't get us wrong. We have a lot of respect for you Jackie.
弗兰克升任之后你一直干得不错
You're doing a fine job since Frank's gone.
也许风格不同  但还是很好的
Different styles, but a fine job.
请诸位稍候片刻
Excuse us just a moment.
他们根本不拿我当回事
They're not taking me seriously.
因为你不是弗兰克
'Cause you're not Frank.
你是说我不是个男人
You mean because I'm not a man.
不  我就是说弗兰克  他们都习惯了做交易
No. I mean Frank. They're used to being offered something.
问问他们有什么要求
Ask them what they want.
我知道保罗在垃圾处理厂的事上需要帮忙
I know Paul needs help with a waste treatment facility.
你也和他们一样瞧不起我
You're being just as condescending as they are.
有好建议送到眼前  就接受吧
Take some good advice when you get it.
我之前就说对了  是不是
I was right earlier, wasn't I?
保罗  雷米告诉我你需要一间垃圾处理厂
Paul, Remy tells me you need a waste treatment plant.
我们在申请联邦基金方面是有点麻烦
We've had some trouble getting matching federal funds.
本  你说你想在选区里盖一座葡萄酒博物馆
Ben, you mentioned once a winery museum in your district?
我们长岛如今的葡萄酒是很不错
We are making some great wines in Long Island these days.
我喝过啊
I've tried some.
跟纳帕[著名酒乡]产的比起来难喝得要死
It tastes like piss, compared to what we have in Napa,
这种东西正好该送进保罗的垃圾处理厂
the sort of piss that belongs in Paul's waste treatment plant.
杰姬
Jackie--
我们刚遭遇了一场疑似恐怖袭击
We have a possible terror attack,
而你们还在这持票待沽
and you're holding out your plate for more pork.
你们真该为自己感到羞愧
You should be ashamed of yourselves.
我治下党团  党员只会因优异表现受嘉奖
In my caucus, people are rewarded for good behavior,
我不会鼓励拿选票换酬金
not trading their votes for ransom.
待会儿进去投票  你们两位都要投赞成
When we walk in there, I expect the both of you to vote 'yes,'
而且要毫不犹豫
without a moment's hesitation.
多谢两位心意回转
Thank you for your change of heart.
只剩六票了
Six more to go.
你离开德州  在著名的菲利普斯学院
You left Texas and, um, spent the last two years of high school
度过了中学最后两年
at the prestigious Phillips Academy.
然后考进了拉德克利夫学院
Um, and then, onto Radcliffe. Yes.
哈佛大学两个本科生院之一  专收女生
就是在那儿  你邂逅了未来的美国副总统
Where you would meet the future Vice President.
他那时只是个帅气的法学院学生
Back then just a dashing law student.
我从没想到过他会成为副总统
I never dreamed he would become Vice President, of course.
有人认为你们的婚姻比你说的要
Some people might think that your marriage may be a bit more
有更多的算计
calculated than you let on,
也许他用得上你家的财富
that perhaps he needed your family's money.
不  不是这样的
No. That's just not true.
你父亲可是为他的竞选投入不菲
Your father did contribute an awful lot to his campaign.
没错  因为他相信弗兰西斯
Yes, he did. Because he believed in Francis.
如果没有你父亲的资助
Would he have won that campaign
他还能赢得选举吗
had it not been for your father's contributions?
这我不清楚  我父亲的资助绝对起了作用
I don't know. I mean, it certainly helped.
但我认为  是弗兰西斯的理念和领导力
But I like to think that it was Francis' ideas and leadership
说服了选民  而不仅仅是竞选广告
that convinced voters, not just TV commercials.
你和副总统已结婚27年了
You've been married for 27 years.
是的
That's right.
你们结婚时还在上学  那时你们都很年轻
You were just in school. I mean, you married so young.
没错  但如果找到了真爱
We did. But when you've found 'the one'…
弗兰西斯就是我的真爱
well, Francis was the one.
你称呼他为"弗兰西斯"
You call him "Francis."
在老家  他们还是叫他"弗兰克"
Well, back home, they call him "Frank," still.
但他喜欢我叫他"弗兰西斯"
But he likes that I call him "Francis."
他说这称呼让他显得更老成
He said it makes him sound more sophisticated.
当政治家的妻子难吗
Is it hard being a politician's wife?
令人兴奋  但也有难处
It's thrilling. Not without its challenges.
甘居幕后  为了他的追求而委屈自己
Always in the background, subsuming your goals for his goals.
我倒不这么看
No, I don't see it that way.
我们都是非常独立的人
We're two very independent people who
只是选择共同经营生活而已
have chosen to live our lives together.
我支持他 他也支持我
I support him. He supports me.
这就回到了政治上的合作的话题上
Which, you know, goes back to the political partnership.
我丈夫的确是位政治家
Well, my husband happens to be a politician,
而我也正好从事政治工作
and I happen to do political work.
但我们的关系远不止如此
But our partnership extends far beyond that.
孩子呢  这是你们做的牺牲吗
Children. Was that a sacrifice?
因为你们还没生过孩子
Because you haven't had any.
弗兰西斯和我献身公共事业
Francis and I wanted to devote our lives to public service.
而我们一致认为投身公职
And we didn't feel that we could both do that
就难以善尽父母之责
and be the parents we wanted to be.
所以我们作了取舍
So, we made the choice.
这回答我们之前听过了
We've heard that answer before.
你说什么
Sorry?
你在以前的访问中给出过一模一样的回答
You have given the exact same answer in previous interviews.
因为这是事实
Because it's the truth.
不好意思  但是"工作"和"时机"
Forgive me, but 'career' and 'timing,'
人们总会找这样的借口
uh, those are often very convenient answers.
从有这个念头到真正去做之间有个过程
It is true that whatever it takes for people to get
而我一直没能走完这个过程
from 'maybe' to 'yes' never arrived for me.
你不觉得有压力吗  没有做母亲的渴望吗
Never felt the pressure? No maternal instinct?
没有
No.
那么这是你的选择  并不是你不能生育
And it was a choice? It wasn't because you couldn't have any?
弗兰西斯和我是为了大局着想
Well, Francis and I did what was right for us.
因为即使是现在
Because it is unusual, I mean, even now,
身在领导层的政治家没有孩子
for politicians at the executive level
也是不寻常的事
not to have children.
是的
Yes, it is.
你丈夫第二次参加国会竞选时
In your husband's second congressional campaign,
有一位反堕胎的共和党候选人
there was a Republican, a pro-family candidate,
他对你们做了一些相当难听的指责
who made some pretty unsettling accusations.
弗兰西斯是一位南方的民主党人
Well, Francis is a Southern Democrat,
我俩的脸皮都很厚
and we have thick skins.
他说  为了保住你丈夫的政治生涯
He suggested, in order to keep your husband's political career on track.
孩子是很多人生活的中心
Children are the center of many people's lives.
我认为他们只是想确保
And I think they just want to make sure that
选出的代表会为了他们孩子的未来奋斗
their representatives will fight for their children's dreams.
而弗兰西斯已经一次又一次地证明了自己
And Francis has, again and again, proven that he will.
作为副总统他也会继续做出努力
And he will continue to do as Vice President.
他还声称在竞选时你可能已经怀孕
He claimed that you may have been pregnant during the campaign.
你当时怀孕了吗
Was there a pregnancy?
你怀过孕吗
Have you ever been pregnant?
-马上停播    -不行
- Break. Now.   - That's not gonna happen.
怀过
Yes.
在竞选期间吗
During the campaign?
之前
Before.
是流产了吗
Was it a miscarriage?
不是
No.
你终止妊娠了吗
Did you – did you terminate the pregnancy?
如果我说"是"
If I said 'yes,'
我丈夫的政治生涯就会面临危险
my husband's political career would be in jeopardy.
我信仰会遭质疑
My faith would be questioned.
同样  我的生活也会受到威胁
Likely, my life would be threatened.
但我不会感到羞耻  是的  我怀过孕
But I won't be ashamed. Yes, I was pregnant.
而且是的  我堕过胎
And, yes, I had an abortion.
能休息几分钟吗
Can you excuse me for one moment?
当然可以  稍后继续为您带来
Of course. We'll have more of our live interview
与克莱尔·安德伍德的直播访谈
with Claire Underwood when we return.
那可需要极大的勇气
That took a lot of guts.
是啊
Yes, it did.
不行  那看上去像是我羞于启齿
No. It'll look like I am ashamed.
但我没有  我也不会
I'm not. And I won't.
你再怎么说都无法挽回
Nothing you can say will make this any better.
我宁愿去解决麻烦...
I'd rather deal with the dama--
我不会逃避这个问题
I'm not going to run from this.
她会问你为什么要堕胎
She's gonna ask why you had the abortion.
不止一次  是三次
I haven't had one. I've had three.
三次  不行  你必须坚称只有一次
Three? No. You need to stick to one.
好吧
Okay, fine.
告诉我你要说什么
Tell me what you'll say.
我不能说出真相
Well, I can't use the real reason.
前两次我还未成年  我做事不顾后果
The first two, I was a teenager, and I was reckless.
那第三次呢
What about the third?
那篇她给我看的文章写得没错
Well, the article that she showed, it's right.
我当时在吃避孕药
I was on the pill.
但没有起效果
It didn't work.
我们讨论过要小孩  最终决定不要了
We talked about having a baby, and then we decided against it.
为什么
Why?
因为我们在专心忙竞选的事
Because we were focused on the campaign.
怀孕多少个星期了
How many weeks in?
16周
Sixteen.
这些你绝不能说
You can't say any of this.
上楼去  我来应付阿什利
Go upstairs. I'll deal with Ashleigh.
如果要继续的话  还有20秒就开始了
If we're going to continue, we've got about 20 seconds.
康纳  我
Connor, I --
请相信我  不然你会犯大错的
Please, trust me. You'll be making a big mistake.
你愿意谈谈当时的情况吗
Are you willing to discuss the circumstances --?
我的怀孕是一次性侵害造成的
I became pregnant as a result of a sexual assault.
你是说你被
Are you saying that you – you were --?
强奸了
Raped.
你之前从没公开说过这件事
You've never spoken about this publicly about this before.
没有人过问
No one ever asked.
你能讲讲发生了什么吗
Can you tell us what happened?
是上大学的时候  一个在和我约会的同学
Uh, it was college. A classmate, we were dating.
发生在...有一次我们吵架了
And it happened on a – We had a fight,
然后他强暴了我
and he forced himself on me.
你和别人说过这件事吗  他被起诉了吗
Did you tell anybody about it, and did he --? Was he charged?
没有  因为当时我觉得错似乎在我身上
No. Because at the time I felt that I was somehow at fault.
我知道我没错
I knew I wasn't,
但我不想被别人指指点点
but... just didn't want to be stared at.
我不想别人叫我"被强暴的女孩"
I didn't want to be known as 'the girl who got raped.'
当发现怀孕的时候  我不想辍学
And when I became pregnant, I wasn't going to drop out of school.
我不想让那个男人毁了我的生活
I wasn't going to let this man ruin my life.
所以我做出了决定  选择堕胎
So I made a choice. I ended it.
但是如果你选择保持沉默
But if you never told anybody about it,
罪犯可能还逍遥法外
the assailant could still be out there.
你能讲讲关于他的事吗
Can you tell us anything about him?
就在几个月前
I saw him, uh,
时隔三十年  我又见到了他
for the first time in almost 30 years just a few months ago.
在哪里
Where?
在弗兰西斯和我出席的授衔典礼上
At a commissioning ceremony that Francis and I attended.
你和他说话了吗
You speak to him?
说了几句  弗兰西斯为他授衔
Briefly. Francis pinned stars on him.
他是授衔者吗
He was being commissioned?
道顿·麦金尼斯将军
General Dalton McGinnis.
我要声明一下  弗兰西斯知道那次强奸
And for the record, Francis has always known about the assault.
只是不知道名字
He just didn't know the name.
这些年来  他一直十分支持我
And he's been nothing but supportive all these years.
我们得和将军取得联系
W—--w--we're gonna have to reach out to the General.
看看他对你的话作何回应
for a response to what you just said.
请问我们能不能  稍事休息
Would you mind if we took a quick break?
当然
Absolutely.
稍后继续克莱尔·安德伍德夫人的访谈
We'll be right back with Mrs. Claire Underwood.
不着急  慢慢来
Take all the time you need.
实验室检验结果全是阴性  先生
The lab tests all came back negative, sir.
那玩意是什么
What was it?
混了面粉的滑石粉
Talcum powder laced with flour.
小麦里的农药让检测呈现假阳性
It was pesticide from the wheat that gave us the false positive.
那我们可以走了吧
So are we're free to go?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
-南茜  告诉他们我这就下楼    -已经告知了
- Nancy, let them 'em I'm on my way down.   - I already did.
-不介意我用你的电话吧    -请便
- Mind if I use your phone?   - Of course.
还有  唐纳德  我会帮你搞到研究资金的
And, Donald? I'm gonna get you that research funding,
无论投票结果如何
no matter how the vote goes.
-你自己看着办  我还是会投反对票    -理解
- It's your call, because I'm still voting against it.   - I understand.
你妻子很勇敢  弗兰克
You have a brave wife, Frank.
你妻子也是  唐纳德
So do you, Donald.
弗兰克
Frank!
你怎么样
How'd you do?
-还剩四个  布莱斯怎么样    -还是不让步
- We're down to four. How about Blythe?   - He won't budge.
你给了他什么好处
What did you offer him?
老年痴呆症的研究经费  他觉得这是侮辱
Alzheimer's research. He was insulted.
投票还有45分钟就要开始了
The vote's in 45 minutes.
我得联系上克莱尔  上车后我该打给谁
I need to get to Claire. Who should I call from the car?
我们没别的办法了
We've exhausted our options.
不说服布莱斯那边  就通不过投票
It's either Blythe's people, or it won't pass.
他们对他太忠心了
They're too loyal to him.
行  去吧  我来解决
Okay. Go. I'll figure it out.
如果需要我  我可以留下来
I can stay if you need me.
不用  去找你妻子  我知道去哪找你
No. Get to your wife. I know where to find you.
南茜  手头所有的纸都给我  再找些推车
Nancy, I need every ream of paper you have. And get me dollies.
就快完成了  还有20分钟
Almost done. Twenty more minutes.
我讨厌撒谎
I hate lying.
-他做了那事吗    -做了
- Did he do it?   - Yes.
那就别内疚
Then, don't feel bad.
要是他否认了呢
What if he denies it?
那就兵来将挡  水来土掩
Then we'll cross that bridge.
-康纳    -再等一分钟
- Connor?   - Give us one more minute.
有个年轻女人打电话来  是内线
We have a young woman on the phone, a private.
她说她也被将军强奸了  两年前
She says she was also assaulted by the General. Two years ago.
她想说出她的故事  但不肯透露姓名
She wants to share her story, but she won't give her name.
如果她不透露姓名  就不能报道
We can't put her on if she's anonymous.
-你想让我说服她吗    -她很害怕
- You want me to convince her?   - She's frightened.
她还在线上吗
Is she still on the phone?
我没和任何人说过
I've never told anyone.
我过了大半辈子  才有勇气说起这件事
It took me almost half my life before I could say anything.
但你现在能说了
But you can say something now.
我不知道
I don't know.
想想还可能有多少其他受害者
Just think of how many others there must have been.
但你想让我说出来
But you want me to talk.
如果你不想说  就不会打电话了
Well, would you have called if you didn't want to?
我没想到还得公开姓名
I didn't think I'd have to use my name.
听着  我理解你害怕后果
Listen, I understand you're afraid of the consequence.
我是个二等兵  而他是将军
I'm a private. He's a general.
而我丈夫是美国副总统
And my husband is the Vice President of the United States.
我们会保护你  我向你保证
We will protect you. I promise you that.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
二等兵梅根·汉纳希
Private Megan Hennessey.
这是什么
What is this?
一旦开销冻结
The names of every person in America
以下所有人就会失去家庭医保
who will lose home care when the Freeze sets in,
失去一半的社会福利
who will lose half of their welfare benefits,
被强迫休假  失去学生贷款
who will go on furlough, who will lose their student loans,
交通服务  战后创伤心理咨询  还要我继续吗
transportation services, post-combat counseling. Shall I go on?
我们得为大局着想  杰奎琳
This is about the big picture, Jacqueline.
这个局面我觉得已经很大了
This picture looks pretty big to me.
我不能投赞成票
I can't vote for the package.
那就别投  你们中有四个人就行
Then don't. Just get four of your people to do it.
避免政府关门后跟我合作
And then work with me after we avoid the Freeze.
我不是弗兰克·安德伍德
I'm not Frank Underwood.
那年至少还有另外两个女孩
At least two other girls that same year.
如果属实  那么他服役的这些年来...
If that was true for all the years he's served...
太让人震惊了
It's just staggering.
而且我觉得非常无助
And I felt so helpless.
然后他一直晋衔  受到体制的保护
And he keeps rising in the ranks. The system protects him.
你觉得为什么从来没有人告过他
Why do you think no one has ever reported him?
你想加入吗
Do you wanna join her?
-我们知道根本没用    -不想
- We know it won't do anything.      - No.
官大一级压死人
Chain of command.
你愿意出生入死地保卫我们的自由
It's inexcusable that you're willing to put your life on the line
然而你却无法自由
to defend our freedom,
说出实情  这实在不可原谅
and yet you don't feel the freedom to come forward.
我热爱我的国家
I love my country.
我也喜欢在海军陆战队服役
And I love serving in the Marines.
但不是这样的
But not like this.
二等兵汉纳希  感谢你今晚如此勇敢  接受采访
Private Hennessey, thank you for your courage in joining us this tonight.
是安德伍德夫人给了我勇气
It was Mrs. Underwood who gave me the courage.
安德伍德夫人  也感谢你的坦诚
And, Mrs. Underwood, thank you, for your honesty.
长官  您夫人来电
Sir, your wife is on the phone.
你给了我们很多需要思考的东西
You've given all of us a great deal to think about.
谢谢你  阿什利
Thank you, Ashleigh.
与克莱尔·安德伍德的
And that concludes our live,
面对面独家专访到此结束
one-on-one exclusive interview with Claire Underwood.
您可以到我们的网站观看完整的专访
You can watch the entire interview on our website.
我们也欢迎您在脸谱网和推特上
And, as always, we invite you to give us your thoughts
与我们进行互动
and your comments on Facebook and on Twitter.
今天的专访就到这儿  感谢收看  晚安
But, for now, thanks for watching. And good night.
结束
And we're out.
这会引起超出你想象的轩然大波
This is going to make waves like you never imagined.
谢谢
Thank you.
卡特呢
Where's Carter?
你现在向我汇报了
You'll be reporting to me now.
那你是谁
And who are you?
卡特的上司
Carter's boss.
嘉文  你干得不错
You're doing good work, Gavin.
但是你不能对目标动手  那可能会让我们暴露
But you can't be assaulting the target. That could compromise us.
我都不知道为什么我们要追查这个人
I don't even know why you're going after this guy.
他根本不入流
He's small-time.
这不是你的事
That's not your concern.
他连写一行代码救自己的命都做不到
He couldn't write a line of code to save his life.
他想发动网络恐怖袭击
He intends to commit an act of cyber terrorism.
那只是个想法  不是能力  他不是真正的威胁
Well, that's intention, not capability. He's not a real threat.
也许卡特会跟你好言相劝
Maybe Carter talked things out with you.
我不会的
I won't.
还要多久
How much longer?
什么多久
Until what?
多久我才能收手
Until I can stop.
你更想进监狱吗
Do you prefer prison?
我帮你抓到了八个儿童色情制作者
I've given you eight child pornographers,
三个僵尸网络病毒制造者
three botnet masters...
但是你还是没有抓到AVunit
But you still haven't given us the AVunit.
我告诉卡特了  我不知道他在哪
Well, I told Carter I don't know where he is.
你知道
Yes, you do.
我不知道  谁也不知道
I don't. Nobody does.
那你在Dec-Sec的朋友呢
Then what about your friends in Dec-Sec?
我不会让你动我朋友的
I'm not giving you my friends.
那你就干这个吧  你是个很有用的线人  嘉文
Then you'll keep doing this. You're a productive asset, Gavin,
但等你没用了  什么律师也救不了你
but the moment you stop being productive, no lawyer can help you.
要是有根真的就好了
Wish we had the real thing right now.
时刻准备
Always prepared.
弗兰西斯
Francis.
我真怀念这样
I've missed this.
我也是
So have I.
你不应该去接电话  听别人夸你吗
Shouldn't you be on the phone getting your accolades?
明天也来得及
That can wait till tomorrow.
给我唱首歌吧
Sing me something.
你想听什么
What do you want to hear?
什么都行
Anything.
*波莉  美丽的波莉*
*Polly, pretty Polly*
*你别觉得我无情*
*Would you take me unkind?*
*哦  波莉  美丽的波莉*
*Oh, Polly, pretty Polly*
*你别觉得我无情*
*Would you take me unkind?*
*让我陪在你身旁*
*Let me set beside you*
*倾诉衷肠*
*And tell you my mind*
*我想和你在一起*
*Well, my mind is to marry*
*永不分离*
*And never to part*
*我想和你在一起*
*Well, my mind is to marry*
*永不分离*
*And never to part*
*初次见你*
*The first time I saw you*
*你让我心伤*
*You wounded my heart*
*哦  波莉  美丽的波莉*
*Oh, Polly, pretty Polly*
*跟我走吧*
*Come go along with me*
*哦  波莉  美丽的波莉*
*Oh, Polly, pretty Polly*
*跟我走吧*
*Come go along with me*
*结婚之前*
*Before we get married*
*共享欢愉*
*Some pleasures to see*
*结婚之前*
*Before we get married*
*共享欢愉*
*Some pleasures to see*
■
2011年《新闻周刊》的一篇报道中指出
美国军队中女兵被战友性侵的可能要大于在战斗中阵亡的可能性
2013年美国国防部的报告认为
美军中每年发生性侵犯案例可能多达1万9千宗
但只有1108名受害者报案
由于军队长官在军内性侵案的调查上有极大的决定权力
所以极少施暴者会受到军法处置
■
2013年媒体揭露美国空军多起性侵案
同时也曝光了一些性侵案罪犯定罪后被主将赦免的案例
引起美国社会广泛关注
美军参谋长联席会议主席德·摩西  国防部长海格
以及美国总统奥巴马都在不同场合对这种现象进行了批判
在国会女性议员的主导下
美国国会在2013年年末通过了新的防止军内性侵的法案
限制了军队长官对性侵案件的干涉